{
  "$schema": "https://mccq.github.io/database/questions_schema.json",
  "questions": [
    {
      "tags": ["player", "item"],
      "question": "How do I detect players with X amount of items?",
      "answer": "@players-amount-items"
    },
    {
      "tags": ["raycasting", "recursion"],
      "question": "What is raycasting?",
      "answer": "@raycasting"
    },
    {
      "tags": ["data pack"],
      "question": "How do I make a data pack?",
      "answer": "@data-pack"
    },
    {
      "tags": ["resource pack"],
      "question": "How do I make a resource pack?",
      "answer": "@resource-pack"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the difference between all the tags?",
      "answer": "@tags-disambiguation"
    },
    {
      "question": "What does TPS mean?",
      "answer": "TPS means **ticks per second**."
    },
    {
      "question": "What does MSPT mean?",
      "answer": "MSPT means **milliseconds per tick**."
    },
    {
      "question": "How can I detect an entity without a score?",
      "answer": "@without-score"
    },
    {
      "question": "Can I run a function after installing a data pack?",
      "answer": "@datapack-install-function"
    },
    {
      "tags": ["block", "container"],
      "question": "How can I detect when a player opens a chest?",
      "answer": "You can detect this using the `minecraft.custom:minecraft.open_chest`. To detect which chest was opened, you need to use [raycasting](@raycasting)"
    },
    {
      "tags": ["advancement"],
      "question": "How do I detect if a certain mob attacks the player?",
      "answer": "You can use an advancement with the `entity_hurt_player` trigger."
    },
    {
      "tags": ["schedule", "delay", "sleep"],
      "question": "How do I run a command after some time has passed?",
      "answer": "@schedule"
    },
    {
      "tags": ["custom model data", "texture"],
      "question": "How can I add a custom item to the game?",
      "answer": "@custom-item"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do I use a score in the name or lore of an item?",
      "answer": "@score-item-display"
    }
  ]
}
